promospro.co.uk 2016-11-28

# Privacy Policy - PromosPro UK

## Privacy Policy

Privacy Statement

PromosPro UK is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our offerings. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. This Privacy Statement only covers the site PromosPro UK.

Personal Data

Only a user's email address is collected when users provide registration to PromosPro UK. By registering, you agree that PromosPro UK may send you periodical emails promoting vouchers and specials from the PromosPro UK merchant base that may be of interest to you. Email addresses are never shared or sold to third-party marketers or third-party agencies.

Aggregated Information

Aggregated information, such as which page users access or visit, and information volunteered by users is collected through various methods. For example, PromosPro UK collects IP addresses; an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers (the computers that "serve up" Web pages) automatically identify your computer by its IP address; when you request a page from PromosPro UK, our servers log your IP address. 

PromosPro UK only uses IP addresses for the purposes of Web traffic analysis and trends.

Use of Cookies

PromosPro UK uses cookies for this site. A cookie is a small data file that most major websites write to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow PromosPro UK to measure activity on the site and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences.

Children and Privacy

PromosPro UK encourages parents and guardians to spend time with their children online, and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children.

Individuals under 13  
No information should be submitted to or posted on PromosPro UK by users under the age of 13 years without consent of their parent or guardian. PromosPro UK does not provide any personally-identifying information for users under the age of 13, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever unless disclosed during collection.

Newsletter & Voucher Alert

PromosPro UK sends newsletter or voucher alerts based on your needs. A newsletter is a periodical email with promoting vouchers from PromosPro UK merchants, regularly once a week. Voucher Alerts are aperiodical emails with promoting informaiton of merchants or products you subscribed to.  
Once you have successfully registered, it means you accept our privacy policy. PromosPro UK may send you voucher alerts and newsletters. If you want to opt out, just click "Unsubscribe Here" at the bottom of our newsletter or voucher alert.

Links to Other Sites

PromosPro UK contains links to sites other than PromosPro UK; those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as PromosPro UK.

Effect of Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party. We may update this privacy policy to this page, and we encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information about our privacy practices.

Contact Us

Please contact us if you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy. You can reach us via the following address: [support@promopro.co.uk](mailto:support@promopro.co.uk)

**USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR CONSENT TO THIS ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE.**
